Guide to the Stanford Museum Collection
Stanford University Library
- Museum objects
  - Ribbons of the Stanford Parlor No. 76 N.S.G.W., 1886 and ca. 1899, ARCH-AM-2004-016 (Box 1)
    016.1 Admission Day, San Jose, 1886 - guest ribbon (faded pink) 016.2 Admission Day, San Jose, 1886 - dark blue 016.3 Stanford Parlor No. 76 with images of Leland Stanford, front of Quad, and unidentified harbor; possibly dated 1899. Attached to metal relief pin at top
  - Road Sign: Alvarado and Escondito, ARCH-AM-2000-066 (Box 1)
  - rock from quarry taken during 1994 tour (see ref. accn. 94-169), ARCH-AM-1994-12 (Box 1)
  - Rocks, papyrus, misc. objects. See box and folder listing- 26 boxes., ARCH-AM-2000-359 (Box 1)
  - Roof tile (clay) from Memorial Church, post 1906, ARCH-AM-1997-023 (Box 1)
  - Roos Bros megaphone, ca. 1945?, ARCH-AM-2003-016 (Box 1)
  - Rooter button, 1924, "Stanford", ARCH-AM-1977-07 (Box 1)
  - Rooters' cap (red felt beanie), ca. 1945?, ARCH-AM-2003-017 (Box 1)
  - Rose Bowl button and Stanford decal (with Lil Injun figure), ARCH-AM-2004-013 (Box 1)
    013.1 Rose Bowl button 013.2 Stanford decal (with Lil Injun figure)
  - Round fans on wooden stick, from Orientation events, ARCH-AM-1998-019 (Box 1)
    AM 98-019.1 and .2 1997 Orientation "Hail, Stanford, Hail!" over picture of inner quad AM 98-019.3 and .4 1998 "Hail, Stanford, Hail!" over the seal; reverse: Opening Convocation program
  - round table, inlaid top, carved legs; said to belong to Jane Stanford and given by her to Lawrence Joseph Connolly during a home remodel, ARCH-AM-1998-002 (Box 1)
  - Royal typewriter, ARCH-AM-1985-11 (Box 1)
  - Rubber stamps (for cancellation) with Stanford Centennial graphics/text, 1991, ARCH-AM-2004-004 (Box 1)
    2004-004.1 "Stanford Centennial Convocation Oct. 1, 1991" 2004-004.2 "Stanford Centennial Celebration homecoming parade Sept. 29, 1991" 2004-004.3 "Stadium Spectacular Sept. 30, 1991" 2004-004.4 "Stanford vs. Colorado Sept. 28, 1991"
  - Runner, Brown, 150X71cm. Fringe on short side. Small red S on each end., ARCH-AM-2000-136 (Box 1)
  - S. U. and Stanford Indian memorabilia, ARCH-AM-1992-14 (Box 1)
    see listing in accn files for 1992-092
  - S.U. t-shirts (6) 1979-80: class of '80; Toyon and Branner Halls; Hopkins Marine Station, ARCH-AM-1997-010 (Box 1)
  - Sample impression from Leland Stanford's seal [intertwined L and S], ARCH-AM-1994-16 (Box 1)
  - Sample of hair felting used as acoustical insulation in Memorial Church (installed ca. 1910, removed 1981), ARCH-AM-2004-029 (Box 1)
  - Samples of bricks and tile salvaged from Palo Alto depot during reconstruction, ARCH-AM-2005-025 (Box 1)
    025.1 original bricks @P5F1 025.2 tile from restrooms 025.3 section of floor tile ""W-floor""
  - samples of wall paper found in/on Branner Hall during renovation, Fall 2002 (5 items), ARCH-AM-2003-021 (Box 1)
  - Sandstone tablet on Redwood base with inscription "Mikhail Gorbachev, June 4, 1990.", ARCH-AM-1993-17 (Box 1)
  - Screen. 46X172 cm. Burlap and tapestry on top., ARCH-AM-2000-148 (Box 1)
  - Seat cushion "Sunset Salutes Stanford University for a Century of Achievement" with the Centennial logo, ARCH-AM-2008-002 (Box 1)
  - Seat cushion from Big Game; pin and cap from Stanford Bookstore, ARCH-AM-1997-019 (Box 1)
  - Seat cushion given out at women's final four basketball championships in Cincinnati, 1997., ARCH-AM-2007-009 (Box 1)
  - See Card File. Verify against item, ARCH-AM-2000-129 (Box 1)
  - Senior Class roll '44, ARCH-AM-2000-041 (Box 1)
  - Senior Class roll '48, ARCH-AM-2000-042 (Box 1)
  - Senior Class roll, '36, ARCH-AM-2000-044 (Box 1)
  - Senior Class roll, '39, ARCH-AM-2000-043 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '40, ARCH-AM-2000-050 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '43, ARCH-AM-2000-051 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '52, ARCH-AM-2000-053 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '53, ARCH-AM-2000-055 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '54, ARCH-AM-2000-054 (Box 1)
  - Senior class roll, '55, ARCH-AM-2000-052 (Box 1)
  - Senior Sombrero '08. G.C.H. on inner band; B. Halsey written inside crown, ARCH-AM-1997-013 (Box 1)
  - Senior sombrero of O. Wayne Mulford '24. Felt field hat by Stetson, leather band with "1924" and "O W M" on sweat band; sold by Roos Bros., ARCH-AM-1977-11 (Box 1)
  - Senior sombrero of Richard Frey. Felt field hat by Stetson, leather band with "Stanford 1924", ARCH-AM-1977-12 (Box 1)
  - Senior sombrero of William A. Ray. Ribbon band; brand mark of John B. Stetson Company on inner sweatband store mark of Wideman's, ARCH-AM-2005-009 (Box 1)
  - Senior sombrero, leather band "Stanford '09", ARCH-AM-1993-12 (Box 1)
  - Senior sombrero. Felt field hat by Stetson, cloth band, no date, with "C M" on sweat band, ARCH-AM-1977-13 (Box 1)
  - Set of labels used for "Bookmaker's Ale," specially bottled beer from the Anchor Brewing Co. served at SUL-sponsored reception at ALA meeting in San Francisco, June 27, 1997., ARCH-AM-1998-012 (Box 1)
  - Shot classes (2) from 1990 and 1991 and coffee mug from Branner Advising Team '01-'02, ARCH-AM-2006-002 (Box 1)
    2006-002.01 shot glass 1990 2006-002.02 shot glass 1991 2006-002.03 Coffee mug
  - Shovel: Green Library groundbreaking, wood handle with bronzed metal spade and handle 40" long., ARCH-AM-1980-24 (Box 1)
  - Shovel: Ruth Wattis Mitchell Earth Science Building;ground breaking- Aug. 19, 1968; Stanford University. 40" high, ARCH-AM-1982-05 (Box 1)
  - Sigma Chi fraternity paddle 1934, ARCH-AM-2003-015 (Box 1)
  - Sign, cardboard. "Room 310- University Archives" 18x55cm., ARCH-AM-2000-333 (Box 1)
  - Sign, framed. "Room 311 Archives Reading Room" frame 28x35cm., ARCH-AM-2000-332 (Box 1)
  - Sign: "Hopkins Railway Library" white painting on black metal. 8x45 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-267 (Box 1)
  - Silkscreen pattern used for the etched glass shades of the historic pendant light fixtures in building 01-30 [made in France], ARCH-AM-2001-23 (Box 1)
    Due to its size, it is currently housed in regular cardboard.
  - Silver case for calling cards given as a wedding gift to Mrs. Van Alstyne from Leland Stanford, with leather carrying case, ARCH-AM-2003-001 (Box 1)
  - Silver cup with "LS" monogram and "44", alleged to have been Leland Stanford's., ARCH-AM-1998-018 (Box 1)
  - Silver pitcher presented to Leland Stanford, ARCH-AM-2000-011 (Box 1)
  - Silver pitcher presented to Leland Stanford by State Agricultural Society for best Holsteins, 1887; ARCH-AM-2000-009 (Box 1)
  - Silver pitcher presented to Leland Stanford for "Elaine", for best 4-yr old record, 1878, ARCH-AM-2000-010 (Box 1)
  - Silver tea set (Reed Barton) used at Roble Hall prior to 1989; each piece stamped (engraved?) with a shield, Roble Club, Stanford University California [held for safe keeping by Porteus while Roble was undergoing earthquake reinforcements], ARCH-AM-2005-047 (Box 1)
    2005-047.1 sugar bowl 2005-047.2 sugar bowl 2005-047.3 cream pitcher 2005-047.4 cream pitcher 2005-047.5 footed serving bowl (7 in. diam.) 2005-047.6 footed serving bowl (7 in. diam.) 2005-047.7 tea pot 2005-047.8 tea pot 2005-047.9 footed round serving platter (11 in.) 2005-047.10 footed round serving platter (11 in.) 2005-047.11 footed round serving platter (11 in.) 2005-047.12 serving tray 2005-047.13 serving tray
  - Silver trophy presented to Norman Dole for world's record pole vault, 1904, by UC students, Stanford-Cal meet. Sterling silver, ARCH-AM-1977-10 (Box 1)
  - Silver vase presented to Willis, 1913, in recognition of friendship from "Comision de Estudios Hidrologicos,Buenos Aires, Argentina" (in square case, lined)., ARCH-AM-1995-09 (Box 1)
  - Silver-plated spoon with "L.S.Jr. University" on handle, ARCH-AM-1992-05 (Box 1)
  - Slice from a limb of oak tree by Mausoleum that was cut down in 1993, ARCH-AM-1993-10 (Box 1)
  - Slide rule used by Hansen, in case., ARCH-AM-1995-26 (Box 1)
  - Small Banner, 17x11 cm. Red felt with white "S"., ARCH-AM-2000-196 (Box 1)
  - Small clipboard and ink blotter, both made from hammered metal (brass or copper), both decorated with university seal. Clipboard bears imprint of Robbins Co., Attleboro, MA, ARCH-AM-2001-27 (Box 1)
    AM 2001-27.1 clipboard AM 2001-27.2 blotter
  - Small red banner (blank), pointed ends - purpose unknown, ARCH-AM-2004-022 (Box 1)
  - Snow globe featuring Stanford University scene, undated; ARCH-AM-2010-010 (Box 1)
    Snow globe: 6.5 inches tall, interior features Hoover Tower, Red Barn, Stadium, The Dish, Memorial Church, the Oval, Red hoop sculpture, and others not so easily identified. Base has version of university seal (no motto).
  - Solar cell and silicon chip from Engineering Library display, undated; ARCH-AM-2008-025 (Box 1)
    2008-025.1 Silicon solar cell in case with attached wiring 2008-025.2 Silicon chip on metal strip which is wrapped around 2nd metal piece 2008-025.3 large square plastic magnifier
  - Sombrero 1910. Soft grey felt hat (brim not as wide as usual); signatures of friends under brim., ARCH-AM-1981-11 (Box 1)
  - Sophomore College t-shirts, 2009; ARCH-AM-2009-041 (Box 1)
    2009-041.1 "Practicing Creativity" brown shirt with orange lettering 2009-041.2 "Practicing Creativity" red shirt with orange lettering 2009-041.3 "Sophomore College 2009" dark green shirt; list of classes on back 2009-041.4 "Sophomore College 2009" light green shirt; list of classes on back
  - Sophomore College t-shirts, ARCH-AM-2010-013 (Box 1)
    2010-013.1 Sophomore College 2001 - red with "SOCO 2001" on back 2010-013.2 Sophomore College 2003 - white with "SoCo 2003" on front and "Oh, the Places You Can Go in SoCo!" on back 2010-013.3 Sophomore College 2004 - black with "18 days + 22 Professors + 284 students" on front and list of names on back 2010-013.4 Sophomore College 2005 - green with "SoCo 2005" and Hoover Tower on front 2010-013.5 Sophomore College 2007 - white with "What level are you trying to reach" on front and list of classes on back 2010-013.6 Bing Honors College A September Studies Program 2010 - purple 2010-013.7 arts intensive A September Studies Program 2010 - maroon 2010-013.8 Sophomre College 2010
  - Sophomore College T-shirts (2), 2002, 2006; ARCH-AM-2009-005 (Box 1)
    2009-005.1 - T-shirt: Stanford Sophomore College 2006 [on back: SOCO 06 Stanford Sophomore College 2006] 2009-005.2 - T-shirt: Sophomore College 2002 [on back: Stanford University]
  - Sophomore dink, ARCH-AM-1981-04 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir matchbook (intact), 13" long illustrated w/ buildings and map inside, ARCH-AM-1995-28 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir matchbook cover 32.5cm long x 5cm, ARCH-AM-1982-04 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir of Stanford University: metal cup with raised images of Mem Chu, entrance gate, Mem Arch, quad arcade, Palo Alto tree. (same as AM 00-192), ARCH-AM-2003-019 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir pennant of the U.S.S.R. - U.S.A. track meet at Stanford Stadium, ca. 1962 (9 inches long), ARCH-AM-2001-26 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir spoon: Memorial Arch, c. 1905., ARCH-AM-1980-22 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir: plastic viewer and key chain. View of Mem Chi. 5x2cm., ARCH-AM-1980-15 (Box 1)
  - Spode plates (13) with Stanford scenes, ARCH-AM-1978-09 (Box 1)
  - Spode plates of S.U. scenes (7): Jordan Hall, between classes, union, arches and library, memorial church, administration building, library front, ARCH-AM-1995-20 (Box 1)
  - Spode plates with Stanford scenes, ARCH-AM-1989-057 (Box 1)
  - Spoon - sketch of front view of Quad [pre-1906] and "Stanford Jr. University" in bowl; CA state seal and "California" on handle, ARCH-AM-2006-017 (Box 1)
  - Spurr, old, 12 X 5 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-145 (Box 1)
  - Squeezable stress-reduction toy in the shape of a Marguerite bus, ARCH-AM-2007-010 (Box 1)
  - Stanford African Students Association t-shirt and trophy, ARCH-AM-2010-004 (Box 1)
    AM2010-004.1 SASA t-shirt, dark grey 2009 AM2010-004.2 trophy from 2008 SASA World Cup
  - Stanford Association Centennial Medallion, 1991, ARCH-AM-1993-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Axe Committee t-shirts (4) 1987-1993, ARCH-AM-2002-24 (Box 1)
    2002-24.1 1987 red, patch with tree over S; polo style 2002-24.2 1989/90 red, patch with axe over S; polo style 2002-24.3 1991-92 red, patch with tree over S over axe; polo style 2002-24.4 1993-94 burgundy, patch with tree over S over axe; polo style
  - Stanford band hat (1956-1962), ARCH-AM-1980-01 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner ca. 1960. Red felt, with "Stanford" in white, Indians across lettering; white felt border. 25 x 43 cm, ARCH-AM-1981-01 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner on bamboo cane, ARCH-AM-2000-169 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Banner on Flag Pole. Pole 3x273 cm long. Stanford seal on Blue Bkg., ARCH-AM-2000-262 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, c.1907, red cloth with "Stanford" in white cloth letters, 3x6'., ARCH-AM-1980-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt with white felt letters, 3 x 6 ft. It hung in Dink Templeton's Encina Room, 1920, 1921; given to donor in 1921., ARCH-AM-1977-03 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt with white felt square, red "S", ARCH-AM-1977-08 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt, "Stanford" in white felt, swallow tail, on black bamboo pole. 38x80cm, crooked pole, 90cm., ARCH-AM-1984-29 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red felt; block letters, double pointed ends. 16 x 31 in., ARCH-AM-1979-10 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red felt; gothic lettering. 14 x 34 in., ARCH-AM-1979-09 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red, 34 x 29 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-50 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner: white letters on square red felt backing, ARCH-AM-1981-08 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner. red felt bkg. with Stanford in white letters. Indian at one end. 74x29cm., ARCH-AM-1980-17 (Box 1)
  - Stanford belt buckle (brass?), ARCH-AM-1995-21 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Block "S" sweater awarded to Dorothy Cone, class of 1928, awarded for women's shot put, circa 1928; ARCH-AM-2007-031 (Box 1)
  - Stanford buttons, 1978-79 (three), ARCH-AM-1980-12 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial items, ARCH-AM-1991-103 (Box 1)
    1991-103.1 paper visor "Stanford 100 Years" 1991-103.2 paper napkins Stanford University Centennial Commencement 1991 (2) 1991-103.3 sew-on patch: Planting for the Second 100 Years Stanford 100 1991-103.4 Button: 100 years of staff diversity 1991-103.5 small trowel, unmarked
  - Stanford Class Shield, 1911. 53X31 cm, wooden shield, Block "S" in brass., ARCH-AM-2000-185 (Box 1)
  - Stanford decals and memorabilia of L. Timothy Portwood, ca. 1975-2008; ARCH-AM-2009-040 (Box 1)
    AM 2009-040.1 football bumper sticker: This is your brain [Stanford helmet] This is your brain on drugs [Cal helmet] AM 2009-040.2 decal: Stanford Fooball more than a passing fancy AM 2009-040.3 pennant from Portwood's retirement party 2008 AM 2009-040.4 plastic cup: 2000 World Series Champions New York Yankees AM 2009-040.5 Pin from Yankee Stadium World Series September 9, 2001 AM 2009-040.6 ticket stub Yankee Stadium World Series September 9, 2001 AM 2009-040.7 Cap (blue and yellow: L M Shop Cap factory, SF) date unknown
  - Stanford diploma and teaspoon, ARCH-AM-1994-10 (Box 1)
    1. 1892 Diploma of V.C. Richards (framed) 2. teaspoon of Memorial Church in Bowl
  - Stanford family portrait in 12 x 16 inch frame (purple velvet with stones), ARCH-AM-2000-058 (Box 1)
  - Stanford flag (red cloth, no lettering) attached to wooden rod, rolled and inserted in wooden case 14" long, ARCH-AM-1982-09 (Box 1)
  - Stanford high power pulsed Klystron with plate that reads: "Dr. Edward Ginzton, our director, co-worker, and friend. From the members of the W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics.; 1949-1959", ARCH-AM-1996-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Hillel T-shirts, ARCH-AM-1996-04 (Box 1)
    1) Red White, Stanford (?) in Hebrew 2) "Killer Maccabees" ) Blue - "Stanford Hillel"
  - Stanford Indian decals: 13 items (4 designs), ARCH-AM-1993-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Indian doll; cloth, with red felt "sweater" with "S"; single red feather. 27 cm tall, ARCH-AM-1981-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford jacket belonging to William A. Stone, class of 1961, circa 1960; ARCH-AM-2010-003 (Box 1)
  - Stanford jacket: red wool with leather sleeves and "Stanford" emblem on left side, ARCH-AM-2002-31 (Box 1)
  - Stanford jewelry, 1922, ARCH-AM-1977-01 (Box 1)
    1. watch fob, "S", class of '22 2. SU tie pin (1922) 3. El Tigre Club lapel pin (1922)
  - Stanford Leather belt and buckle 1924, ARCH-AM-1979-04 (Box 1)
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-1996-12 (Box 1)
    Pillow cover Bookends (3 sets) Belt buckle Placard with Stanford seal Stanford seal with pin
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2000-042 (Box 1)
    042.1 Red felt banner with STANFORD in white; PEG '23 written on lower right corner 042.2 Granite paperweight keepsake from Pace program "For Service to Stanford 1961-1964" 042.3 Granite paperweight keepsake from Pace program "For Service to Stanford 1961-1964"
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2004-008 (Box 1)
    008.1 framed printed illustration of Memorial Church, pre-06 008.2 tip tray, ceramic, made in Germany, with image of Mem Church (no steeple) 008.3 Stanford belt buckle with seal (very worn) 008.4 glass bottle from University Pharmacy, F. J. Steinmetz, Palo Alto, ca. 1905 008.5 ceramic tray (small) with east arch of S.U., made in Germany for Oscar Promis, San Jose
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2005-024 (Box 1)
    024.1 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.2 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.3 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.4 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.5 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.6 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.7 Playing cards with U. seal, 2 packs in box 024.8 Playing cards with U. seal, 2 packs in box 024.9 Pour spout for liquor bottle with carved Indian head wearing red beanie with "S"
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2006-006 (Box 1)
    006.1 wooden box (5.75 x 3.75 in.) with CUE at Stanford burned into top 006.2 Stanford Think Again cube (unfolds into assorted images) 006.3 Paperweight: The President's Fund Stanford University 1993-1994 Founding Member (brass seal of U. imbedded in plastic or clear resin?) 006.4 Four assorted Centennial pins 006.5 Label pin with tree on it 006.6 Pin of mortar board (black enamel) inscribed on back ""B.J.D. 1948""
  - Stanford memorabilia - athletic and alumni, ARCH-AM-1993-01 (Box 1)
    Two tumblers: Coach of the Year - 1951 - Chuck Taylor Four tumblers: Class of 1927's 50th Reunion (1977) Indian Joe doll, with drum (battery operated) Plaque on stone: "for service to Stanford 1961-64" Stanford PACE program Glass pitcher engraved with AEO [Alpha Epsilon Theta]
  - Stanford memorabilia: 6 pennants (3 with seal, 3 with Indian head), 1 banner, tennis bag, Indian doll and stuffed horse, cap printed with the 1984 football schedule, ARCH-AM-2006-004 (Box 1)
    2006-004.1-.3 Pennants with U. seal 2006-004.4-.6 Pennants with Indian head 2006-004.7 Banner: "Stanford" with U. seal 2006-004.8 Cap with football schedule 2006-004.9 Bag, red white striped canvas with "Stanford Tennis" 2006-004.10 Indian doll, wearing shirt with red "S" 2006-004.11 Stuffed horse (red) with white "S" on each hip (brand reads "A College Pet") 2006-004.12 Button: Class 1944 Once an Indian Always an Indian (with Lil Injun face)
  - Stanford memorabilia: beanie and megaphone, ca. 1931; football pins, ca. 1963, ARCH-AM-2002-25 (Box 1)
    2002-25.1 freshman beanie, red felt 2002-25.2 Roos Brothers megaphone [poss. originally blue and gold] 2002-25.3 football pin "Stanford Indian" with football charm 2002-25.4 football pin "Stanford Indian" with helmet charm 2002-25.5 football pin "Stanford Indian" with helmet charm (flat)
  - Stanford mugs and shot glass, miscellaneous, ARCH-AM-2010-008 (Box 1)
    2010-008.1 Stanford Humanitites Center mug; design copyright 2001 by davey hubay 2010-008.2 Clear plastic mug with "STANFORD" in red letters and 3 pennant shapes below 2010-008.3 Shot glass "Branner Hall 1991-1992" with image of a penquin
  - Stanford of Today printing die, unknown; ARCH-AM-2010-001 (Box 1)
    Metal printing die, badly damaged.
  - Stanford pennant, c. 1960 with Lil Injun caricature, red felt, with white painted design., ARCH-AM-1980-03 (Box 1)
  - Stanford pennants; athletic sweaters 1919-21, ARCH-AM-1979-13 (Box 1)
  - Stanford pins owned by Jennie Hughes Hutchison, class of 1910, ARCH-AM-1995-08 (Box 1)
    1. Phi Beta Kappa pin 2. Pin of S.U. seal with "10" also on it 3. Stanford Pennant pin
  - Stanford seals, ARCH-AM-1981-06 (Box 1)
  - Stanford student hat (George A. Tarbell), 1906; ARCH-AM-1988-02 (Box 1)
    Red wool hat, somewhat like a Fez, with tassle; '06 written on it. G. Tarbell '06 written on inside brim.
  - Stanford sweatshirt, c. 1960: Red, hooded (child's size), in white on front "Stanford" with Lil Injun symbol., ARCH-AM-1980-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford sweatshirt, red with slightly modified U. seal on front, circa 1968; ARCH-AM-2009-020 (Box 1)
  - Stanford the Game (board game), ARCH-AM-1985-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Think Again cube, unfolds into different images, 2001; ARCH-AM-2009-025 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Tree costume worn by Judy Mischel, 1980-82., ARCH-AM-1984-04 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University 119th Opening Convocation fan (program), 2009; ARCH-AM-2009-039 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University 3-ring binder ca. 1950. Reddish brown with "STANFORD UNIVERSITY" stamped in gold on lower right edge, ARCH-AM-2004-001 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University book cover: seal on front, S INDIANS on spine, and L'il Injun on back; plasticized paper, ARCH-AM-2005-005 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University embossing and foil stamping dies, unknown; ARCH-AM-2009-031 (Box 1)
    2009-031.1 University seal, inch 2009-031.2 University seal, inch 2009-031.3 University seal, 7/8 inch 2009-031.4 University seal, 1 and 1/8 inch 2009-031.5 University seal, 1 and inch 2009-031.6 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.7 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.8 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.9 Seal with lone tree, 1 inch 2009-031.10 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.11 Letter S, 3 inch tall 2009-031.12 Shield for Medical School, 1 inch 2009-031.13 Hoover Institution, 2 inch 2009-031.14 Lane Medical Library (image of Hopkins with Hopkins Medical Library arched over portrait) 3 inches tall 2009-031.15 University seal with lone tree, 3 inches 2009-031.16 University seal with lone tree, 5/8 inch (2 items) 2009-031.17 Herbert Hoover Medal for Distinguished Service 2009-031.18 University seal, 5/8 inch (2 items) 2009-031.19 University seal, 5/8 inch 2009-031.20 University seal, 1 3/16 inch 2009-031.21 University seal, 1 3/8 inch 2009-031.22 University seal, inch 2009-031.23 University seal with lone tree, 1 inch 2009-031.24 Shield for Medical School, 7/8 inch 2009-031.25 Shield for Medical School, 1 3/16 inch 2009-031.26 Plate with four 1-inch University seals
  - Stanford University leather postcards, ARCH-AM-2010-009 (Box 1)
    2010-009.1 to Miss Irene Withers; features Stanford coed and RAH-RAH-RAH STANFORD, with other notes 2010-009.2 to Miss Jennie Withers; features large red S, with notes 2010-009.3 to Miss Jennie Withers; features candle, book, pennant, with notes 2010-009.4 to Miss Jennie Withers; features coed holding pennant and RAH-RAH-RAH STANFORD, with other notes
  - Stanford University seal (metal) on wooden plaque originally owned by Henry Dorrance Owen, Class of 1912, circa 1910; ARCH-AM-2010-014 (Box 1)
    Metal University seal (8.25 in. diameter) with Die Luft... on wooden shield (14 in. high)
  - Stanford watch fob 1924, ARCH-AM-1979-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanfordopoly game, 1989 2nd edition, ARCH-AM-2001-11 (Box 1)
  - Stereoptican, made by Underwood Underwood., ARCH-AM-2000-255 (Box 1)
  - Stereopticon viewer, ARCH-AM-2000-038 (Box 1)
  - Sticker on Grand Opening of Stanford Bookstore, May 1991, ARCH-AM-1995-04 (Box 1)
  - Sticker; 11x11 cm. red, yellow, black. Palo Alto Shell Gasoline; with Mem Chu and Stanford S., ARCH-AM-2000-203 (Box 1)
  - Sticky Wilson Candy Boxes, ARCH-AM-2008-021 (Box 1)